[{"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "You think he's arrogant?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "I think it's an indispensable relationship, that's how I would put it.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "How important are we in the scheme of things?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "I think he's a great president.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "How do you think he's doing as president?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Now, if that had happened now or on any presidential visit that I was involved in or now is happening, the slick second- nature of these visits, if anything goes wrong like that, there would be a national outcry.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "-- the Americans were calling --", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Did you ever do this?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "-- the Americans were calling the tunes.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "When you had President Bush?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I don't think he would appreciate my singing talents.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Were President Bush and you ever around a piano?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so, but I think you've got to distinguish between the rightness of the case -- and, of course, the UN and the whole world supported the rightness of the case -- and then the follow-through.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Was the war in Iraq, given all we now know, was that a mistake, do you think?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I think the royal family is incredibly popular in America.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Is part of the special relationship between Britain and America connected to the royal family, do you think?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I think it's about Britain.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Why do you think Americans are so fascinated by the British royal family?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "I think it was a tragedy what happened to Princess Diana.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "When you saw what happened to Princess Diana, who you knew -- and I knew, for that matter -- and we saw the attention that she got and the relentlessness of it, leading to the terrible event of her death, do you worry about the attention, now, on William and Kate, these new superstars of the British royal family?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I think that was important, but I think you've got to look forward, as well.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Did you get that sense?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "You see, for 50 years, the IMF was dealing with national problems.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "When you think about the IMF for a moment, how important is the IMF to the global economy?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Very important.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "-- since the financial crisis?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I'm way beyond all that.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Why don't you take over the IMF?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Well, I was in charge of --", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Way beyond it?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I don't think it comes to that, to be honest.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "If you were offered the job, would you take it?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, I think we've got these big problems that require people to take a longer-term view than just their own selfish individual or national interest.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Yes and --", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Has the Internet eroded political power in the conventional sense?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "It's because of the Internet that we know about events in Burma, we knew about the fraud elections in Zimbabwe, we knew about many different things that were going on in Egypt.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "So, you're seeing, now, people power, driven from the floor up, aren't you?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "I think foreign policy cannot be conducted by a few elites that just talk to each other and never consult the public.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Is it the end of despotic rule as we know it?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "No, because Pakistan is the epicenter of terrorism.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Were you surprised when you heard that?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "The question in Pakistan is, you've got the army, you've got the security services, you've got the politicians, you've got the business class.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Do you think anybody at high level in Pakistan would've known that Osama bin Laden was there?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I can tell you what I don't miss.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "And finally, what do you miss most about being prime minister?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "There certainly is a trust deficit, but it has been persisting since the last one year.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "How would you describe the relationship as it stands?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "To an extent, yes.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Do you accept that?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, that's a very -- when you say I worked there -- no, I was trained there.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Is it credible that no one else in that base, in all this time, would have had any idea?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "There's normal.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What I'm suggesting is does it seem likely to you, with all these military intelligence people around this compound, that nobody knew anything?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Would you have been happy about that?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, I would have certainly reacted, very angrily.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "How would you have reacted if you had been Pakistan's president?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "It is absolutely illegal, yes.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Is it, therefore, illegal what the Americans did?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Now you are getting into the legality of -- he was a world class risk.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "So it was an unlawful assassination?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Is that what you are saying?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Well, no Pakistani and no leader in Pakistan will allow this as a justification for any intrusion into Pakistan.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Why, if you are President Obama, could you possibly take the risk under those circumstances of not acting unilaterally?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "You think he was arrogant?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Theoretically, technically, yes, indeed.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Would you see another raid by the Americans to get rid of another al Qaeda terrorist in exactly the same circumstances, without informing the Pakistani government -- would that be an act of war?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Yes, I have already taken a decision.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Will you consider doing that?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Well, I have entered into politics because I do believe I can win.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Do you believe you can win?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I didn't say act of war.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Are you worried that if you ramp up the rhetoric over the search for the terrorists in Pakistan against the Americans, they might respond and say, we're yanking our money?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Do you believe the current Pakistani administration has been 100% honest?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I would have done something to turn the tables in my favor.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "You mean you would have traded the information that you had bin Laden?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "You wouldn't have just handed him over to the Americans?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "I would have used this card to my favor.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Wouldn't that be the responsible thing to do?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Let's not get into the details of something which didn't happen.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "If you had known for a fact where bin Laden was, would you have handed him over to America?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "USHARRAF: I would like to take action.", "docId": "110526pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "If you go back into power and you become president again, and you discover that a senior member of al Qaeda, who has without any doubt been committing atrocities, is living in another compound near Karachi or somewhere, would you tell the Americans?", "qSentId": 586}]